本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
好汉两个半
第十二季  第四集
翻译：帅气诱惑赛太公   可爱诱惑YY猫   阿蘅阿蘅   泪点无限低的大菜
校对：帅气诱惑赛太公   可爱诱惑YY猫  总监   YY猫
后期：灰灰是菇凉  时间轴：YY猫
波塔  早安
Oh, hey, morning, Berta.
警告一下  男人在干活中
Little warning, man at work.
这里弄弄  那里搞搞
Doing a little banging and screwing.
也警告你一下
Little warning for you.
在酒吧待到凌晨两点的女人也是"东搞西搞"
Woman at bar until 2:00 A.M. doing the same thing.
你是在干嘛
What are you doing?
给房子装婴儿保护装置
I am baby-proofing the house.
领养机构的要求
It's a requirement of the adoption agency,
而且这也是好事
and it's a good thing, too.
这厨房简直是杀婴神器
This here kitchen is a death trap.
这里有一大堆能弄死人的东西
Whole mess of things up in here that can kill someone.
有刀  有火  毒清洁剂  滚烫的沸水
We got knives, we got fire, poison, scalding hot water,
艾伦过期的鱼肉卷
Alan's leftover fish tacos.
你紧张过度了
You worry too much.
杰克当年没少吃到地板蜡跟清洁剂
Jake ate a steady diet of floor wax and detergent,
你看他...
and he turned out...
其实你说的还真有道理
Yeah, maybe it's not a bad idea.
我把所有的柜子跟抽屉都固定了
I locked all the cabinets and the drawers,
炉灶也加上了安全开关
put these safety knobs on the stove,
如果你想要拿出那些化学药品
and if you want to access any chemicals,
会需要用特殊的磁力钥匙
you will need a special magnetic key.
对了  你洗衣服的时候
Oh, by the way, when you're doing the laundry,
留意有没有特殊磁力钥匙掉出来
keep your eye out for a special magnetic key.
为什么毛巾抽屉也要上锁
Why would you need to lock the towel drawer?
你的大麻是藏在药物抽屉里的啊
You hide your pot in the medicine cabinet.
我猜的
I'm guessing.
那不是普通的毛巾抽屉
That is no ordinary towel drawer.
那是灾难的起源第一步
That's the first step on the stairway to disaster.
我太醉  懒得听这些狗屁
Oh, I'm too hungover for this crap.
好吧  好吧
Okay, okay.
你想象一下  小孩拉开这个抽屉
All right, imagine, if you will, child pulls out the drawer,
爬上去到台面上  在爬过去
climbs up onto the counter and toddles over to the window
到没锁的窗边
that has been left open
没锁是因为艾伦觉得蒸花椰菜让他反胃
because Alan finds the smell of steaming broccoli
所以打开窗透气
to be "gaggy."
结果呢  小孩看到了美丽的风筝
Whereupon, the child spots a beautiful kite,
很可能是蝴蝶或皮卡丘图案的
most likely in the shape of a butterfly or a Pikachu.
小孩伸手想抓风筝
The child reaches for the kite,
滚出窗外
tumbles out the window,
掉到雨篷  弹出去  飞在空中
bounces off the awning, flying through the air,
本来马上要死了
heading toward certain death,
结果奇迹发生
when, miraculously, it is caught
他被光上身的马修·麦康纳接住了
by a shirtless Matthew McConaughey.
"别担心  你的小孩一切都会很好
"Don't worry, your baby's gonna be all right,
很好  很好"
all right, all right."
知名男演员  在1993年他出演的电影《年少轻狂》中
有着著名的台词"all right, all right, all right"
是啊
Yeah, sure.
我们这次是走运  孩子没事
You know what, we got lucky this time,
但我们不能每次都有马修·麦康纳来救啊
but we can't depend on McConaughey every time.
行啊  但我以后要把你的大麻藏起来了
Okay, I'm gonna have to start hiding the pot from you.
不怕一万  只怕万一
Better safe than sorry.
每个楼梯间  每个厕所  每个尖锐角落
Every stairway, every toilet, every sharp corner
都被锁上  闩上或加垫了
has been locked, latched or padded.
没人可以在这个家里受伤
No one is getting hurt in this house.
烫
Hot!
烫  烫
Hot! Hot!
很好  很好  很好
All right, all right, all right.
你也看到了
So, as you can see,
我在楼梯口装了安全门
I installed a gate at the top of the stairs,
楼梯底下也装了安全门  为了额外小心
at the bottom of the stairs, and as an extra precaution,
我在楼梯中间也装了一个
I put one in the middle of the stairs.
好还要更好
Overachiever.
我想他只是想关住我  怕我跑掉
I think he's just trying to keep me from getting away.
你的婴儿防护措施做得很棒
Well, you did a great job baby-proofing.
我想象不到有谁在这家里能受伤
I can't imagine anyone getting hurt in this house.
是吗  你试试说我穿这牛仔裤显胖
Really? Try telling me I look fat in these jeans.
够了  收了你的神通吧  霹雳火
Okay, flame off, Human Torch.
所以下一步是怎么样呢
So, uh, so, what do we do next?
挺简单了
Oh, well, it's pretty simple.
我走到外面阳台等
I walk out onto the deck,
你就把一叠百元大钞放桌上
you put a pile of hundreds on the table,
我走进来  把钱塞进皮包里
I come back, slip them into my purse,
小孩就是你的了
and you get a kid.
我车库的工具箱底有5千块钱
I have $5,000 in the bottom of a toolbox in the garage.
我开玩笑的
I was joking.
我也是
As was I.
我本来不打算在审核完毕前
Anyway, uh, I wasn't gonna say anything
告诉你们俩这消息的
until you guys passed the inspection,
但貌似我们已经找到了
but it looks like we may have found
适合你们两个的孩子了
a potential match for the two of you.
我们
We're...
我们要有孩子啦
We're getting a baby.
你是说真的吗  太不敢相信了
Are you serious? This is unbelievable.
别着急  目前还只是在
Well, slow down; all that's happened so far
一名怀孕的妈妈看过你们的资料
is a pregnant mother has seen your profile
很想见见你们
and wants to meet you.
有人看过我的资料还想见我吗
Somebody saw my profile and wants to meet me?
跟在相亲网站上差好多哦
That's so different than the dating sites.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe this.
她是谁  哪里人
Who is she? Where is she from?
她几岁了  肚子里是男是女
How old is she? Is she having a boy or a girl?
别  别说说说说说
Wait, no, la-la-la-la-la!
我不想知道  我想有惊喜
I don't want to know. I want to be surprised.
沃顿  你想太多了
Walden, you're getting ahead of yourself.
你是说女孩吗
Did you say girl?
我好像听到你说是女孩
I thought I heard you say girl.
算了  其实呢
Wait, no, you know what?
根本无所谓
Doesn't matter.
只要手脚健全
Ten fingers and ten toes--
这才是最重要的
that's all that matters.
你不说话是因为是个男孩吗
Are you not saying anything 'cause it's a boy?
天啊  我们要有儿子啦
Oh, my God, we're having a boy!
沃顿
Okay, Walden,
当你见到孩子生母
when you meet the mother,
你最好看起来是很冷静  镇定的父亲
you want to come off as a calm, stable father.
不是去参加贾斯丁·比伯演唱会的14岁少女
Not like a 14-year-old girl at a Justin Bieber concert.
抱歉  我们是太兴奋了
Sorry, we're just really excited.
没事  我懂  我也很为你们兴奋
No, I get it. I'm excited for you.
等见面时间确定好了  我再通知你们
I'll call you when the meeting is set up.
对了
Oh, and by the way,
我觉得你穿那条牛仔裤  看起来超棒
I think you look fantastic in those jeans.
姑娘  我们绝对会是好闺蜜
Girl, we are gonna be BFFs.
我们要有孩子啦
We're gonna have a baby.
We're gonna have a baby!
我们要有孩子啦
我们得庆祝一下
Oh, we have to celebrate.
我去车库里面拿点香槟
Uh, I'll go to the garage and get some champagne.
太好了  我们要有孩子啦
Great! We're gonna have a baby!
我们要有...
We're gonna have a...
等等  我们车库里没有香槟啊
Wait, we don't have champagne in the garage.
我藏钱的工具箱
My toolbox!
艾伦
Alan!
给
Here.
我买了这个给你
I got this for you.
为啥
Why?
如果我们穿着情侣毛衣
I think it would be nice
去见宝宝的母亲  那更有说服力呀
if we wore matching sweaters to meet the birth mom.
情侣装哦
Twinsies.
我们应该是以已婚夫妇的身份
We're supposed to be a married couple,
而不是理发店四重唱的两位团员
not half of a barbershop quartet.
不能两者兼具吗
Can't we be both?
* 麦克马丁小姐  赐我一个孩子 *
* Miss McMartin, bring me a kid *
* 跟你结婚  真是一件蠢事*
* Marrying you was a dumb thing I did *
你唱太低了
You were flat.
你说那位母亲  会不会很辣
So, the mom-- you think she's hot?
她都怀孕九个月了啊
She's nine months pregnant!
我知道啊
I know.
孕妇诱惑超正点
Love me some preggos.
胸围38  腰围62  臀围38
38-62-38.
宝贝真是有前有后啊
Baby got back and front.
听着
Okay, listen.
如果想要这女孩把孩子给我们
If we want this girl to give us her baby,
她一定要认为我们是一对合适的人选
she has to think that we're a well-adjusted couple.
如果她感受到你那股猥琐劲儿
If she gets a creepy vibe off of you,
她肯定会立马转身逃跑
she's gonna turn and run the other way.
我之所以这么说
And I'm only saying this
因为我深受你那股猥琐劲儿毒害
'cause I'm getting a creepy vibe off of you.
你自己上网搜"海伦·米伦露点照"  还好意思说
Says the guy who Googled "Helen Mirren nip slip."
1945年出生  一生得过无数奖的英国女演员
海伦是永恒的女神
Helen is timeless.
听着  如果你搞砸了
Now, listen. If you mess this up for me,
我一定会让你生不如死
I will make your life a living hell.
现在记住  我们深爱彼此
Now, remember, we love each other.
你好  妈妈
Hello, Mama.
你们好
Hi.
你就是凯西吧
Hi, you must be Kathy.
欢迎来到我们的马里布梦想豪宅
Yes, uh, welcome to our Malibu dream house.
他是肯
He's Ken.
那我岂不就是芭比了
Oh, I guess that makes me Barbie.
我是沃顿
I'm Walden.
他是艾伦
This is Alan.
快进来
Come in.
外套给我吧
Here, c-can I take your coat?
谢谢你
Oh, thank you.
瞧瞧你
Look at you!
-孕味十足呀  -挂衣服去
- So very pregnant. - Coat.
我知道
I know.
我从七月开始就没见过自己的脚
I haven't seen my feet since July.
我鞋子是一对吗
Am I wearing matching shoes?
貌似还真不是
Actually, no.
但是一点都不突兀  很可爱啊
Uh, but you know what, it works. It's cute.
快请坐
Um, please sit.
对啊  你感觉如何
Yeah, please. How you feeling?
我的膝盖超肿
My ankles are swollen,
我的背超疼  更别说我的胸部了
my back hurts, and forget about my breasts.
我都没注意到  因为我是同性恋嘛
I haven't even noticed, you know, 'cause I'm gay.
那是...
That's...
那是我的彩虹勇士
That's my rainbow warrior.
总是在挥舞他的性向旗帜
Always waving his flag.
即使跟任何事无关也要提
Even when it relates to nothing.
聊聊你自己吧
Um, so, uh, tell us about Kathy.
我想你们应该了解我的第一件事是
I think the first thing you should know about me
这个  并不能代表我是什么样的人
is this is not representative of who I am.
我刚从加州大学洛杉矶分校毕业
See, I just graduated from UCLA.
这孩子是因为春假时去拉斯维加斯怀上的
The baby is a result of a spring break trip to Vegas.
我猜在拉斯维加斯发生的事
Ah. I guess what happens in Vegas
都留在你肚子里了
stays in Kathy.
是啊  我花了六个月的时间才知道
Yep, took me about six weeks to figure out
我每天早上的晨吐
that my morning sickness
不是一场久达六个月的超级宿醉
wasn't just a really bad hangover.
我们都会犯错误
Well, we all make mistakes.
某天早上我醒来  就发现自己跟这货结婚了
One morning, I woke up married to this one.
主要是因为这不在我的五年计划之内
See, bottom line, this wasn't part of my five-year plan.
我的五年计划是念法律学校  当法官文员
You know, law school, clerk for a judge,
开始我的事务所
start my own practice.
哇  真是野心勃勃呀
Wow, that's-that's impressive.
艾伦的儿子  杰克
Uh, Alan's son, Jake,
也有一个念完十年级的五年计划
had a five-year plan for the tenth grade.
瞧  这就是为什么我喜欢你们
See, that's why I liked your profile.
你当过父母
You have parenting experience.
我也喜欢你的幽默感
Your sense of humor came through.
我有点喜欢你们是同性恋了
And I kind of love that you're gay.
肯定不及我们喜欢自己
Not as much as we do.
-对吧  沃沃熊  -对的  艾艾猫
- Right, Wally Bear? - That's right, Alley Cat.
即使我不能参与宝宝的人生
Even though I'm not gonna be part of the baby's life,
但我也想做它唯一的妈咪
I like the idea of being the only mom.
这点我完全能理解
I can totally understand that.
可能是因为我妈妈是个冷漠毒舌的酒鬼
Probably because my mom was an ice-cold, sharp-tongue alcoholic
喜欢整天购物和做美容  不喜欢跟我一起玩
who preferred shopping and spas over spending time with me.
这点我完全能理解
And I can totally understand that.
跟我聊聊你们吧
So, tell me about you.
你们为什么想要组建家庭
What made you guys decide to start a family?
抚养我的儿子
Uh, well, raising my son
是我这辈子最重要的人生经历
was one of the greatest experiences of my life,
我想沃顿也能拥有这份喜悦
and I just wanted Walden to feel that same joy.
是啊  对我而言有两个原因
Yeah, I mean, for me it's a couple reasons.
一是我感觉我人生好像缺少点什么
I-I felt like something was missing in my life,
我想要回馈社会
and I wanted to give back,
二是有了孩子  我才能用多人合用车道
and having a kid will allow me to drive in the carpool lane.
高速路上一条只允许两个人以上乘坐同一辆车使用的车道
能开怀大笑真好
It's nice to laugh again.
不过我刚笑尿了一点在你们的沙发上
Except I just peed a little on your sofa.
我帮你拿东西擦吧
I'll get you something.
其实我手边正好有东西可以擦
Oh, uh, actually, I got something right here.
宝宝刚踢了我一下
The baby just kicked.
我感觉到了
I felt it.
看来你肚子里住这个足球明星啊
Oh, looks like someone's got a little soccer star in there.
天啊  你味道真好闻
God, you smell good.
艾伦  你想抬起头呼吸下新鲜空气吗
Alan, you want to come up for some air?
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我太兴奋了
Just got excited.
-因为宝宝  -当然
- About the baby. - Sure.
那么凯西
So, uh, Kathy,
你知道肚子里的是男孩还是女孩吗
uh, do you know if it's a boy or a girl?
我不知道  但你们的档案写
I don't, but your profile said
你们没有性别偏好  不是吗
you didn't have a gender preference, right?
是的
Oh, that's right.
就像我20多岁时  男女通吃
Just like me in my 20s.
你们俩太好玩了
You guys crack me up.
你们一定会是很棒的爸爸
You're gonna make great dads.
根据我买的马克杯  应该是世界上最棒的爸爸
Oh, world's greatest, according the coffee mugs I bought.
那就好  因为我已经决定了
Well, that's good, because I made up my mind.
我要你们领养我的孩子
I want you to have my baby.
-不是吧  -是的
- No! - Yes.
天啊  你说的是真心话吗
Oh, my God! You did not just say that!
你个小贱人
You bitch!
谢谢  凯西
Thank you, Kathy.
谢谢  拉斯维加斯
Thank you, Vegas.
谢谢  破掉的套套
Thank you, broken condom.
你可以谢谢果汁店买一赠一的龙舌兰酒
Well, you can thank two-for-one tequila shots at the Tropicana.
别忘了肚子里那个小家伙哟
Let's not forget this little guy.
你感受到它动了吗
Do you feel it moving?
我能感觉到"它"在"变大"
I can feel it growing.
迎婴聚会最好的礼物
Okay, best shower gift:
巴里  孩子的第一支烟枪
Barry. Baby's first bong.
对
Yep.
和孩子的尿片一样
And just like the kid's diaper,
里面都是邪恶[恶臭]的绿色东西
it's full of stinky green stuff.
披萨马上到
The pizza's on its way.
在这个时候  谁想喝点啤酒
In the meantime, uh, who wants a beer?
好啊
Yeah.
开始喝吧
There we go.
沃顿  你会是一个好爸爸
Walden, you are gonna make a great dad.
艾伦  杰克是你养大的
And, Alan, you've already raised Jake,
所以  你就反着来养这个孩子吧
so I guess just... do the opposite.
我仍然不敢相信
I still can't believe it's even possible
两个男人也能生孩子
for two men to have a baby.
这到底是什么时代啊
What an age we live in.
科学太先进了  对吧
Science, right?
拉里  这孩子不是我们生的
Larry, we're-we're not actually having a baby.
是我们领养的
We're adopting.
放"空枪"哈[无精或弱精症]
Ah, shooting blanks, huh?
如果艾伦怀孕了
Well, I guess if Alan gets pregnant,
你肯定就知道他偷人了
you'll know he's been cheating on you.
你俩真的结婚了
So you two are really married, huh?
-对啊  -很疯狂吧
- Yep. - Yeah, crazy, isn't it?
不  我告诉你们什么才是疯狂
No, I'll tell you what's crazy.
你从来也没想泡过我  沃顿
You have never hit on me once, Walden.
我们每天一起工作  面对面
I mean, we worked together every day, side by side,
从来没有长时间的对视过
and not so much as a lingering glance
也没听你说过"你今天挺帅  巴里"
or a "Gee, you look nice today, Barry.
"你是不是瘦了  巴里"
"You lost a little weight, Barry?
"这条工装短裤很显你的小腿肌肉  巴里"
Those cargo shorts really flatter your calves, Barry."
不是的  老兄
No, man.
我们结婚是为了领养一个孩子
We got married so I could adopt a baby.
我们是假夫妻
That... we're a pretend couple.
就像你"在加拿大的女友"
It's kind of like your "Girlfriend in Canada."
拜托  奥利维亚是真的
Okay, Olivia is real.
好吧  看她发给我的裸照
I mean, just... Okay, look at these nude photos she sent me.
这是詹妮弗·劳伦斯[奥斯卡影后]
That's Jennifer Lawrence.
老是有人说她像
She gets that all the time.
再过几天  我就是一位父亲了
In a couple days, I'm gonna be a dad.
我即将为一个
I'm gonna be completely responsible
毫无自理能力的人
for the emotional and financial well-being
提供感情依托
of someone who is completely incapable
和财产保障
of taking care of themselves.
谢谢你一直扮演"婴儿"的角色让我练手
Thank you for being my test baby.
我希望是个男孩
I'd keep my fingers crossed for a boy.
为什么
Why?
很简单的数学问题
Well, basic math.
如果你有个儿子  你只需要担心一个鸡鸡
If you have a boy, you only have to worry about one penis.
如果你有个女儿  你就得担心所有男人的鸡鸡
You have a girl, you have to worry about them all.
无论如何  你们都会爱孩子
Either way, you're gonna love it.
当爸爸是世界上最幸福的事情
Being a father is the best thing in the world.
你的孩子多大了
How old are your kids?
我儿子15岁
Well, my son is 15
我的私生女今年满11岁
and my secret daughter is going to be 11 this year.
你的私生女
Your... your secret daughter?
对  她和我的情妇长得很像
Yeah, she looks a lot like my secret wife.
孩子就是这么神奇
You know, kids are amazing.
你得把所有的知识都传授给他
You know? You get to pass all this knowledge down
塑造他的思想意识
to this little person and-and shape their mind.
比如  如何向女孩搭讪
Like, you know, how to talk to girls
朋友需要你的时候  如何支持他们
and how to be there for your friends when they need you.
你也可以教他们每回结账的时候
Oh, you can teach them your ability to always be in the bathroom
总能刚好在厕所的本事
whenever the dinner check comes.
那是本能
That's pure instinct.
教不了的
Can't be taught.
我所有的回忆都跟我爸相关
You know, all my memories revolve around my dad.
他把我的电子宠物扔到垃圾处理机里
The time he threw my Tamagotchi down the garbage disposal.
他和我的舞伴调情
Time he made a pass at my prom date.
他和我妈离婚  娶了我的舞伴
Time he divorced my mom and married my prom date.
各位  各位  是医院打来的
Guys. Guys, it's the hospital.
如果是我的病人  说我不在
Oh, if it's one of my patients, I'm not here.
别担心  如果我是你孩子的医生
Oh, don't worry. If I'm your kid's doctor,
我不会这么做
I won't do that.
都是这么说的
It's what you say.
凯西快生了
Kathy's in labor!
我们得走了
We got to go!
我叫车
I'll get an Uber.
我去拿儿童座椅
I'll go grab the car seat.
我去拿尿片包
I'll get the diaper bag.
天啊  那是送披萨的小哥
Oh, God, that's the pizza guy.
艾伦
Um... hey, Alan,
你能把钱给披萨小哥吗
could you pay the pizza guy?
我在厕所里
I'm in the bathroom!
他怎么做到的
How does he do it?
很感谢你们能来
You know, I-I appreciate you guys coming,
但是你们不必留下来
but you really don't have to stay.
开什么玩笑  我们愿意留下来
Are you kidding? We want to be here.
有言道
You know what they say.
"养一个娃  竭全村的力"
"To raise a child, it takes the Village People."
各位
Hey, guys?
我可能抽得太猛了
I think I may have gotten way too high.
谁能送我去医院吗
Can somebody take me to the hospital?
你这不就在医院嘛
You're in a hospital.
你怎么做到的
How'd you do that?
为什么我们什么声音都没听到
I wonder why we haven't heard anything.
他们把凯西带去产房  有一个小时了吧
They took Kathy to the delivery room, like, an hour ago.
有时候  婴儿就是不想出来
Sometimes the baby just doesn't want to come out.
你设身处地想想
I mean, put yourself in its position.
九个月以来
For nine months, you've been floating
你一直沉浸在世界上最好的水床里
in the world's nicest waterbed.
突然有个人打开了活门
Then somebody opens a trap door,
水全部流走了
all the water flows out,
一把钳子把你钳住
a set of salad tongs grabs you by the head
把你拽出来
and yanks you out,
然后一个你从未见过的男人
and then some guy you never seen before
开始拍你的屁股
starts slapping you on the ass.
让我想起我去提华纳[墨西哥]的那次旅行
Reminds me of a trip I took to Tijuana once.
看她多可爱啊
Aw, look at how cute that one is.
对啊  奶子也不错
Yeah, she's got a nice rack, too.
你在看什么呢
What are you looking at?
那个性感的护士  你们在看什么
The hot nurse. What are you looking at?
那个孩子
That baby.
你们真变态
Ugh! You guys are sick.
你们给孩子取名字了吗
So have you guys decided on a name for the baby yet?
-没  还没  -还没
- Oh, no, not yet. - No.
压力挺大的
It's such a big responsibility.
我不想给他取一个
I don't want to give him a name
会被其他小孩取笑的名字
that other kids can make fun of.
不幸的是  每一个名字都会被取笑
Well, bad news. Every name can be made fun of.
这不可能
That's not true.
是吗
Really?
沃顿  你的湖还好吗
How's your pond, Walden?
沃顿湖位于美国马萨诸塞州
比较有深度的嘲讽  不过还是挺伤人
It's an intellectual insult, but it still stings.
我中学的时候被人叫做"牙仙拉里"[音似]
I was "Larry the fairy" all through high school.
不是吧  我是"牙仙巴里"
Oh, no way! I was "Barry the fairy."
有人把我的名字艾伦
Somebody noticed that you could rearrange
重新排列后  就变成了
the letters of "Alan," And I became
"小肛门·哈勃"
"Little Anal Harper."
我的名字是"赫伯"[草药]
My name's "Herb."
大家没有费劲想哏
Kids skipped the clever puns
就直接把我脑袋塞在马桶里
and just shoved my head down a toilet.
肯定有很多名字
Well, I'm sure there are plenty of names
是不会被小孩拿来取笑的
that kids can't make jokes about.
两位哈勃-施密特先生
Mr. and Mr. Harper-Schmidt?
这姓氏也不用担心被人笑
Yeah, nothing to worry about there.
两个基佬爹的姓氏用连字符连住而已
Just the hyphenated last name of the two gay dads.
凯西怎么样了
So how's Kathy?
她很好
She's doing fine.
好的还有你们刚出生的儿子
So is your brand-new baby boy.
天啊  我们有儿子了
Oh, my God, we got a boy!
我可以把杰克返厂换新了
I get a do-over for Jake!
我只用担心一条鸡鸡了
I only have to worry about one penis!
我喜欢穿女人内裤
I like to wear women's underwear!
什么
What?
我以为大家是在坦白秘密
I thought we were confessing things.
他来了
There he is.
他鼻子像你  眼睛像艾伦
He's got your nose and Alan's eyes.
拉里  我告诉你了...
Larry, I told you before that...
谢谢  拉里
Thank you, Larry.
看他  多神奇
Look at him. He's so amazing.
想不出现在还有什么能比
I can't think of anything more beautiful
就这么看着他更美好的事了
than what I'm looking at right now.
是啊  说的太对了
Yeah. Mm-hmm. It's true, that's the truth.
但如果那俩俏护士现在开始亲热
But how much more beautiful would it be
是不是会更加美好
if those two nurses just started making out right now?
是啊  说的太对了
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah.
你还好吗
How you doing?
挺好的
I'm good.
除了累
Tired.
还有疼
Sore.
看这个小男子汉
Look at this little guy.
能让我抱抱吗
Can I hold him?
当然
Uh, sure.
他是世上最美的东西
Oh, he is the cutest thing ever.
来来  击个掌吧
Hey, hey... high-five.
算你欠我的
You can owe me.
欢迎降生到世界  小家伙
Welcome to the world, little buddy.
我们会有很多欢乐的
We're gonna have so much fun.
一起去玩球
We're gonna go to ball games together
一起去游泳
and go swimming together
一起去泡...泡椒凤爪
and pick up chick... ens together.
笑一个  快
Smile. Come on.
好
Okay, uh...
看看这照片
Oh, oh, oh. Look at that picture.
全世界最帅的两个男人
The two most handsome men in the world.
都是我的
And they're both mine.
怎么了
Oh, what's the matter?
可能想找妈妈了
Uh, maybe he wants his mommy.
好的  来妈妈这  小宝贝
Oh, all right, come here, little buddy.
我是说他可能饿了
Uh, I think he might be hungry.
当然了
Oh, of course.
对  没错
Oh, yeah, of course.
来  给你
Okay, here.
抱住
There.
我已经开始思念他了
I miss him already.
是啊  爱不释手
Yeah, it's hard to let him go.
其实是  无法放手
Actually, it's impossible.
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
等等  刚刚发生什么了
Wait. What, uh... what just happened?
我错过剧情了吗
Did I... did I miss something?
她准备留下孩子
She's keeping the baby.
那法学院怎么办
But what-what about law school?
五年计划呢
The-the five-year plan?
当我看到这个小家伙之后...
After I saw this little guy...
计划就变了
the plan changed.
以前我无法想象有他的生活是怎样的
I mean, before, I couldn't imagine my life with him.
现在我是无法想象没有他会怎样
Now I can't imagine it without him.
但...他会是一个出色的父亲
But... but he's gonna be a great dad.
-艾伦  -不  他爱他
- Alan... - No, no. H-He loves him.
艾伦  这...
Alan, it's...
好吧  我们直接说点实际的
Okay, let's-let's just approach this practically.
孩子多少钱
Um... how much for the kid?
我有
Uh, I have, uh,
有32美元
I have $32 on me.
我得留3元去超商买晚饭
I'm gonna need three dollars for dinner at AMPM,
剩下的都归你了
but the rest is yours.
我说真的  我也很难过
Believe me, I feel terrible.
你还难过
You feel terrible?
我们要开着婴儿安全椅没人坐的车回家
We're-we're gonna be driving home with an empty car seat.
你知道等我们到家会面对什么吗
And you know what's waiting for us when we get there?
一间空婴儿房和一张空婴儿床
An empty nursery. An empty crib.
一个空...
An empty... uh, uh....
那瑞典东西叫什么来着
What's that Swedish thing
那个能穿在身上的育儿袋
that, uh, that you wear like a pouch,
你可以像袋鼠一样带着宝宝
to carry your baby around like a kangaroo?
比约登背带
Bjorn.
一个空比约登背带
An empty Bjorn!
一个蓝色的空比约登背带
An empty blue baby Bjorn!
发音难  面对它更难
Hard to say, but even harder to face.
艾伦  别说了
Alan, just... stop.
没关系
It's okay.
换成是我也不会放弃他的
I wouldn't be able to give him up either,
所以我不会怪你
so I don't blame you.
真的吗
Really?
我懂  你是他的母亲
I get it. You're his mom.
让你经历这些事真是非常抱歉
I'm so sorry to put you through all this.
不用抱歉
Don't be sorry.
他很幸运
He's... lucky.
你们都很...幸运
You're both... very lucky.
这就是个圣人
This man is a saint.
他妈的大圣人
A damn saint.
我们走
Let's go.
说再见  艾略特
Say good-bye, Elliot.
-听着像"挨虐的"  -艾伦
- More like "Smelliot." - Alan.
你还好吗
You doing okay?
好
Yeah.
再给我看看他的照片吧
Can you show me the picture of him?
行了  你别再给自己找罪受了
Oh, please, don't put yourself through this.
求你了  就再看一次
Come on, just one more time.
好吧
Okay.
给
Here.
看看他
Look at him.
完美的宝贝
He's perfect.
很遗憾这计划没有成功
I'm sorry this didn't work out as planned.
他还欠我一个击掌呢
He still owes me a high-five.
别担心
Don't worry.
我们会找到孩子的
We'll find our kid.
我知道
I know.
与此同时  你还是我老公
In the meantime, you're still married to me.
没错  我还是
Yes, I am.
为什么凯西不把你带走  孩子留给我呢
Why couldn't Kathy take you and give me the baby?!